<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My Resume</title>
    <link>https://jifuliya.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My Resume</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 21:05:37 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jifuliya.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Yulong Liu</title>
      <link>https://jifuliya.github.io/resume5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 21:05:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jifuliya.github.io/resume5/</guid>
      <description> Welcome to my resume, you can click the company name to see my project experience. Thanks </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self Introduction</title>
      <link>https://jifuliya.github.io/resume6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 21:05:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jifuliya.github.io/resume6/</guid>
      <description>Undergraduate University of Electronic Science and Technology of China(UESTC)
Major: software engineering
master Southwest Jiaotong University
Major: software engineering
Introduction Like to exercise like reading like reading like programming like to study all new things, have good communication ability, have a complete product development experience, always believe in a word, if you do not limit yourself, there is no limit to limit yourself.
Working life 3 years
Tel 13981777612</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beijing Qisike Network Technology Co Ltd.</title>
      <link>https://jifuliya.github.io/resume1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 21:05:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jifuliya.github.io/resume1/</guid>
      <description>Project experience (2017.4 - now): Shoplex (click to google play with shoplex) 1.Shoplex is an electric business crowd-funding app, mainly for overseas markets, Shopping zone in Google Play Southeast Asia to the top sixth, The number of users exceeds 20w+. I participates in all life cycles of this app, including initial positioning, design, medium-term client architecture, and functional iterations, and later data burial points, analysis and advertising, etc.
2.Project technology: Response programming is adopted to centrally collect and handle the exception of the client and modularized each functional module (Key word: Rxjava, Mvp, Dagger2, Retrofit2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ThunderSoft</title>
      <link>https://jifuliya.github.io/resume2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2016 21:05:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jifuliya.github.io/resume2/</guid>
      <description>Project expirence: System independent app GAPP-FileManager&amp;amp;Sprint Main responsibilities:
1.Independently responsible for PhotoPicker&amp;amp; storage entry / document / image browsing &amp;amp; development of encrypted entries, and late packaging interfaces with other independent app.
2.Each Sprint cycle is 2week, which is responsible for the split plan of the corresponding functional module stroy&amp;amp;task.
3.Responsible for maintenance of application modules, development of new requirements and writing of corresponding functional documents.
4.Undertake owner responsibilities in the late stage of the project, communicate with SPM and VPM, and release APK weekly and official version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ZhiChun Network Technology Co Ltd.</title>
      <link>https://jifuliya.github.io/resume3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2015 21:05:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jifuliya.github.io/resume3/</guid>
      <description>Project expirence: Zhi Chun (based on campus activity social networking APP), has been on-line application store. Main responsibilities:
1.Realize data display through RecyclerView+Fragment+SwipeRefreshLayout+ViewPager.
2.The Retrofit+Rxjava framework is adopted.
3.Use the three level cache mode to load and cache the pictures.
4.Is responsible for integrating the SDK IM function of the circular letter, including chat &amp;amp; new message prompts badage&amp;amp; contact list;
5.Responsible for integrating Baidu map SDK to get the geographic location and realizing the identity binding of the corresponding location through positioning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fa Su You Yun</title>
      <link>https://jifuliya.github.io/resume4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2011 21:05:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jifuliya.github.io/resume4/</guid>
      <description>Projects: Overseas cross-border commerce and trade(Chief Operating Officer) I.Main responsibilities: 1., responsible for communication with franchisees and customers.
2.Responsible for personalized design and website maintenance
3.Responsible for the operation of the company</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>